you're not going to do like that
no hey guys uh Brett contas here I am
with Natalia Melo she is the uh 2012 Miz
bikini Olympia so uh she's known are you
known for having the best glutes on man
Brazilian she's Brazilian so here's
Natalia hello and um and okay we were
talking about glute training and she
told me something very interesting about
Brazil and I was like yes so I want her
to tell the story so okay okay Natalia
first of all Natalia where are you have
a Facebook page yes my Facebook page is
www.fb.com SL Natalia with n a t h a l i
a mow
fit and my G my Instagram is the same
and face uh Twitter it's all the same
Natalia Melo fet I'll post the links for
you guys on this blog so sorry I speak
too fast okay so elaborate on Brazil
when you're you're Natalia is from
Brazil and uh do you guys just do the
squat is the squat the end I'll be all
for glutes no absolutely not that's one
thing that um I thought was very cool
about your videos and everything because
I saw somebody here in the states
doing something other than squats and
showing what we're using to doing in
Brazil like in Brazil you're gonna have
a whole session of of the gym just with
uh glutes glutes machines and we also
have the ankle weights that goes up to I
don't know like 30 40 lbs for you to do
uh Kickbacks and and stuff like that so
and the first thing that I looked for
when I moved here was for the ankle
weights and I couldn't find them I'm
like where did they go that is oh that's
so exciting to me because I I have ankle
weights and I always thought they they
provide a great glute workout you get on
all fours you do different things and
yeah yeah and like because they they did
I couldn't find ankle weights here I had
to make some adjustments from the
exercise that I knew from
Brazil uh with the on the cable with the
ano strap yep so you will have uh a
portion of the gym for just glute
training in Brazil oh I'm in heaven when
I go there I'm like what am I going to
do today that one this one they're like
15 machines just getting glutes in a
like all different angles yep and um
here in the United States the gyms are
not set up for building glutes that well
well here is still a lot better than
Europe because I'm currently living in
Europe uh right now I'm here in Arizona
just prepping for the Olympia so like
that's whenever I went to my my gym
there it's a super nice gym but they
don't have the culture of having
machines for glutes so I had to make
even more adjust Ms there because here
sometimes you go to a gym they have the
kickback machine and and and like the
ankko straps for each the cable there I
couldn't find ano straps I couldn't find
the kickback machine so I had to like
work around it y but here is still a lot
different than it is in Brazil though
yep so uh we will be doing some uh
exercises today uh with Natalia and I
will uh put them up on the blog as well
so uh once again Natalia melow uh follow
her on Facebook and Instagram and uh be
sure to check her out she's competing
next month uh trying to for four weeks
trying to defend her title so yes wish
her luck byebye guys